{
    "id": "2db2eaea177045cda5e76c7d574484fd",
    "title": "Body Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you put your …………………….. foot forward you’ll succeed in the interview.",
            "description": "To put your best foot forward is to make a favorable impression. ",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "right",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "269172acd4e94c25a3a9d2084165dd48"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has an interview tomorrow and she is pulling her …………………………. out.",
            "description": "To pull your hair out is to be very worried about something",
            "answers": [
                "hair",
                "eyes",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4165260f07041e0b128630222a9c157"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before accepting the job offer, she made it clear that she must have a free …………………………",
            "description": "When you have a free hand you have the power to do what you want. ",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "voice",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "57fcba68defb4cecb3f73e2976f29882"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no …………………………….. in running the company.",
            "description": "To have a hand in something is to be involved in it.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "part",
                "hands"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acb1295f6dab4008b7c916b1d51a89ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "In almost all societies rich people still have the …………………………. hand.",
            "description": "To have the upper hand is to have power and control over someone or a situation.",
            "answers": [
                "bigger",
                "higher",
                "upper"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a4b998a874ae484490ce6999467c40be"
        },
        {
            "question": "The robbers were caught …………………………… while trying to sell the stolen goodies in the market.",
            "description": "To get caught red-handed is to get caught while doing something illegal or wrong.",
            "answers": [
                "black handed",
                "red handed",
                "handcuffed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "141c01c5ff1048b8bbc75df5a0efe2e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man and his sons work hand in ……………………………..",
            "description": "When two people are hand in glove, they have an extremely close relationship.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "glove",
                "mill"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35d198f0ffd2493a8bbb088c84c7b469"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got his ……………………… rapped for talking too much in the class.",
            "description": "To rap someone’s knuckles is to give him a light punishment so that he wouldn’t repeat the same offence.",
            "answers": [
                "elbows",
                "knuckles",
                "fingers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4818291451043a5aa79aa7fc232fb08"
        },
        {
            "question": "So it is your debut tonight. Break a …………………………..",
            "description": "It is a phrase used to wish someone good luck.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "foot",
                "leg"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e7b30b6ba367422283d751d7e777796e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t believe what he says. He is just pulling your …………………………..",
            "description": "To pull someone’s leg is to subject him / her to a playful joke or hoax.",
            "answers": [
                "feet",
                "hand",
                "leg"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e207c9859ce47b0b06aa717860c04bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She thought she had got that role but in the end they chose to cast someone else. There’s many a slip twixt .......................................... and lip.",
            "description": "This is an expression used to imply that things can wrong at any time.",
            "answers": [
                "mug",
                "cup",
                "glass"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e21bcc0fb624126899ad5aa80ae5a52"
        },
        {
            "question": "That thought had never crossed my ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "heart",
                "mind"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be3dd376bad54bbeb58a4587f7b95e1d"
        }
    ]
}